Omega Man: A Wrestling Love Story is a documentary,
tv movie film directed by Yung Chang.
Tyson Smith, better known as his in-ring name Kenny Omega, took the long and
unorthodox road to achieve his dream of pro wrestling stardom.
Follow his journey to the top of the wrestling world as he defies not only the odds
but people's preconceived ideas of what a professional wrestler can be.
Himself (as Kenny Omega), played by Tyson Smith.
Tyson Smith (born October 16, 1983), better known by his ring name Kenny Omega (Japanese:
ケニー・オメガ, Hepburn: Kenī Omega), is a Canadian-born professional wrestler.
He is signed to All Elite Wrestling (AEW), where he
is the leader of The Elite stable.
He also serves as both an active talent and an executive vice president.
Known for his in-ring ability and technical prowess, he is regarded as
one of the best professional wrestlers in the world.
Before joining AEW in 2019, Omega was known for his tenure in New Japan Pro-Wrestling (NJPW) from 2014 to 2019, during which he held
the IWGP Heavyweight Championship, IWGP United States Heavyweight Championship, in addition to various other titles.
He was also a former member and leader of the Bullet Club stable.
He incorporates elements from video games in his persona.
Throughout his career, Omega has also performed as part of independent promotions worldwide, including DDT Pro-Wrestling, Jersey All Pro Wrestling,
and Pro Wrestling Guerrilla, as well as larger promotions, such as Ring of Honor, Impact Wrestling, and Lucha Libre AAA Worldwide.
While wrestling in the latter two promotions, he held the Impact World Championship and AAA Mega Championship, and during the
spring and summer of 2021 he held the AEW World, Impact World, and AAA Mega titles simultaneously as a triple champion.
In AEW, he has held the AEW World Championship once, the AEW World Tag Team Championship once, the
AEW World Trios Championship twice, and the AEW International Championship once.
He became AEW's inaugural Triple Crown winner in September 2022 by winning the World Trios title, and also became
AEW's inaugural Grand Slam champion by winning the AEW International Championship in March 2025.
Widely regarded as one of the best professional wrestlers in the world, Omega was named Sports Illustrated's Wrestler of the
Year in 2017 and topped Pro Wrestling Illustrated's list of top 500 male wrestlers the following year and in 2021.
He has also attained the latter publication's Match of the Year distinction three times; one of those matches, in which Omega competed against Kazuchika Okada in a two out of three falls match at
Dominion 6.9 in Osaka-jo Hall in June 2018, received a seven-star rating from sports journalist Dave Meltzer, the highest rating Meltzer has ever awarded a professional wrestling match.
He was inducted into the Wrestling Observer Newsletter Hall of Fame in 2020.
He is an overall eight-time world champion in professional wrestling.
The film explores themes of wrestling, wrestler,
pro wrestling, engraved on a nation.